Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure...
Blast it!
Oh no, the exit's blocked with ice!
And more is coming this way!
Hey, shit!
It's time to cover the whole tunnel!
I gotta find a way out of this death trap!
What?
No, my paw!
I can't rip my paw loose!
Let's go.
All right, the sun is about to set.
Didn't Shade say three hours?
Guess that cocky beggar had a bit more
trouble finding Dio's
mansion than he thought.
Can't say I was expecting
this to happen, though.
Right, Avdol?
I have a bad feeling.
Maybe it's better if he doesn't
find that accursed mansion.
Hmm? Hmm?
You see, maybe he hasn't come
back, because he did find it.
Hmm.
What are you saying?
It didn't occur to me until a moment ago,
but a stand user is likely
to be guarding Dio's lair.
We may have put that beggar's
life in grave danger,
if he hasn't already been
killed. What? Are you serious?
Son of a...
I barely made it out of there.
And my...
my leg is...
That ice caught my paw like a bear trap.
I'd be dead if I hadn't gnawed it off.
I think I'm gonna hide
out here for a while.
If I'm down here long enough,
maybe Bird Brain will go away.
After this is over, the Speedwagon
Foundation can make me an artificial leg.
But I'm still pissed as hell.
Damn that bird.
You're not getting away with this.
I'm gonna make you suffer
for what you did to me.
Just you wait.
Wait, that sound!
Something out there dove into the water.
No way.
Birds have the capacity
to dive underwater.
Like humans and canines, birds are
reliant upon lungs for respiration.
But the average bird
has five to six air sacs
stored away in its chest
and stomach regions.
It's these pockets of air
that give birds the ability to
remain conscious at altitudes
of six to seven thousand meters,
a feat completely impossible for humans.
Even if it were to be strangled,
a bird can survive for several minutes
thanks to its internal air reserves.
With these advantages, a bird can survive
underwater much longer than a dog.
It sounds like something's
headed straight for me.
But how?
That's impossible.
I don't understand what could
be coming after me down here.
Wait a sec.
Could it be?
It's that bird again.
But how can it survive
underwater like this?
That bastard.
Where'd it fly off to now?
It's closing in.
But what's its plan?
More icicles?
One, two, three! Great!
Three icicles are coming this way!
Suck on that, you freaking coot!
Yes, I did it.
How do you like that?
The icicles are stopping
the wall from leaking.
But at the rate they're spreading,
they're going to cover everything.
No, what am I going to do now?
I know what it's doing.
It's focusing on freezing
the water around me.
And it's cut my air pipes.
I don't think it's trying to suffocate me.
Its real plan is to bury me alive.
It's no use!
It's collapsing!
This bird is too powerful
for me to hold it off!
And much worse, I'm surrounded
by ice and freezing water!
Just my damn luck!
So much for finding a decent hiding
place to lay low in for a while!
No other choice!
I have to dig my way out! Give me a break!
This stupid day has gone from bad to
horrifying in the worst possible way!
First I lose my leg and now some demon bird
wants me flattened into a frozen dinner!
Damn, I can't hold it off anymore!
I'm about to be crushed!
I need to dig myself out of here now!
Huh?
What is that?
It looks like someone dug a
tunnel down here. But why?
It's getting ready to
shoot another ice missile.
Damn it my stand is being held by the ice.
I can't defend myself and
there's nowhere for me to escape?
Wait, that's it!
Either way, you slice it, it's Tarot time!
I'll let the dome break!
And use the air pressure to catapult
me forward like a spitty bullet!
I got out of there alive.
That dumb bird didn't have to
die, but it left me no choice.
One of us had to go.
But it looks like this
will probably be the end
for me I've been bleeding
out for a while now.
I hardly have enough strength in
my body to keep myself afloat.
Let alone make it back to shore
which means I'm gonna drown.
Why is this happening I was supposed
to live a trouble-free life?
Orchestra plays.
Damn it, I messed up.
Thank goodness I found you.
As soon as I saw that little face and
those great big ears, I knew it was you.
It's that stupid bird's
fault that you're like this.
It attacked you just like my dogs.
You're going to pull through this.
The bird's gone, so there's
nothing to worry about.
Try to hang on, all right?
Keep fighting.
I'll patch you up right away.
The bird.
Pet Shop Stand Horus.
Status deceased.
Damn that mangy mutt, where
the hell did he run off to?
He's got to stop pulling stunts like this.
I'm starting to get worried,
he's been gone for a while.
That lousy fleabag.
Jotaro, what's the matter?
There must be someone following us again.
Not quite, but I thought I heard a voice.
Like someone's calling out to us?
A voice?
It's... Iggy!
Iggy!
What on earth happened?
Look at that.
He's got injuries all over his body. Hey!
Iggy's missing his front leg, too!
You think he got run over by a car?
He's not the kind of dog
that gets into car accidents.
You were attacked by
the enemy, weren't you?
What's this?
It looks as though someone
treated his wounds.
I have to say, they did a great job.
But it wasn't Iggy that I heard.
Whoever was calling out to
us was definitely human.
Iggy did have a run-in with the enemy.
When we found him,
he was half-dead in the arms of a boy,
so the Speedwagon Foundation
doctors saw to his wounds.
They did the same.
For my eyes. It's you!
You're finally back!
It's Kakyoin!
Good to see you, Kakyoin!
How's it going? Kakyoin!
Tell me, how are your eyes treating you?
I'm glad you're all safe.
We missed you, pal.
So, they were able to treat you?
Yes, I'm ready for action.
While it's true I'll have a few
scars, my eyesight is back to normal.
We're all really glad to hear that.
Jotaro.
Where do you think you're going, Iggy?
He may have been quite indifferent
toward humans and stands in the past,
but now it looks like he's
trying to lead us somewhere.
I'm not aware of all the details surrounding
his encounter with the enemy stand,
but judging from his resolve,
this is about revenge.
Maybe, but that still doesn't
explain where he's taking us.
Hang on, Iggy!
Wait for us!
I recognize that car.
It's the same fancy ride the beggar was
driving C-could this
wreckage mean that he...
But how?
What's strong enough to tear a hole through
a car like a piece of wet newspaper?
It would seem as though I was
right to be concerned about him.
He should have never been involved.
Is it possible this is the handiwork
of the Stan user Iggy fought earlier?
All signs seem to point to
that being the case Huh? Iggy!
What the hell's going on?
All of a sudden, I'm
drenched in a cold sweat.
And there's this oppressive
feeling of doom roaming in the air.
I don't know about you guys,
but I am majorly creeped out.
Where exactly is Iggy trying to take us?
I know where he's going, this feeling.
It's all too familiar to me.
This aura is pure, unmitigated evil.
It's the mansion from the picture.
We've arrived.
Iggy, you're able to find it by yourself?
What lay before Jotaro and
the others was something
more sinister than anything
they'd previously faced.
They would soon look
upon the source of their
predicament and the
very embodiment of evil.
The path that had led them
here was long and arduous.
Foreign lands shrouded in
mystery and treacherous
stand-using assassins
met them at every step.
Each battle was a struggle for survival,
where the wrong move would
spell out certain death.
There were tears, laughter,
sadness, rage, and joy.
The journey affected them all.
Now,
nearly 50 days have passed
since the team departed
Japan on their quest to save
the life of Jotaro's mother,
Holly.
Everything led to this.
The time had come to
defeat Dio and end the
100-year curse afflicting
the Joestar family.
Joseph was determined to
save his daughter, Holly,
and nothing and no one was
going to stand in his way.
Kakyoin vowed to remain resolute.
He would defeat Dio not only to save
Holly, but to overcome his own weaknesses.
Avdol was steadfast in his conviction,
considering it his personal duty to
root out evil wherever it lurked.
Polnareff was determined to make
the tyrant Dio suffer for turning
him into a puppet and forcing
him to betray his own principles.
Iggy's spirit was untamable.
He knew his life of turmoil
could be traced back to
a single man and was Intent
on making sure the bastard
faced his wrath and so in
other words if we Beat the
shit out of Dio in there this
damn nightmare will be over
once and For all that's
right and their scent of evil
confirms that he's here he's
Hiding inside the mansion
like the coward he is it's
hard to believe but we We've
finally reached the end of
this hellacious journey.
All right, man, you ready?
The gate's open as if
they're inviting us in.
This is totally different
from the situation yesterday.
Now that I think about
it, if I can sense Dio,
then it stands to reason that he
has the ability to sense us too.
If we try to enter the
mansion guns blazing,
no doubt we'll be playing
right into the enemy's hands.
Before we do anything, we
need to think of a strategy.
Careful, the door is opening!
Everyone on guard!
Check it out.
What's with this weird corridor?
It must go on forever.
This can't be real, right?
It has to be some sort
of trick or illusion.
Listen, Polnareff, no matter
what, don't go through the door.
Dio's probably got a couple more stand-users
waiting in the wings to fight us.
Hey!
Something's coming this way!
Wait, is that guy floating?
Is he a stand-user or what?
Master Joestar, welcome to our abode.
We've been expecting you, sir.
I am the resident butler of the mansion.
Thank you.
I'll wager that Star
Platinum's first attack will...
Let him have it already, Jotaro!
I'm entering the turn at full speed!
You're saying if we don't defeat you,
we won't be able to get
back to the real world?
You've pieced it together, good sir!